Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1954-2016 and undated
  - K-P, Misc. Correspondence, 1990-2014 (Box 72)
  - Kahneman, Daniel, 1999-2010 (Box 8)
  - Ka-Ke, 1975-2013 (Box 8)
  - Kalfon, Pierre, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Kalman, Peter, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
  - Kalt, Joseph, 1981-1986 (Box 8)
  - Kamoike, Osamu, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Kandori, Michihiro, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Kaneko, Mamoru, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Kantorovich, Acad. L. V., 1979-1983 (Box 8)
  - Karlin, Samuel, 1986-2009; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Karni, Edi, 1980-1984 (Box 8)
  - Kast, Robert, 1980-1988 (Box 8)
  - Katzner, Donald, 2009 (Box 8)
  - Kelly, Jerry S., 1983-1993 (Box 8)
  - Kelsey, David, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
  - Kennedy, Donald, 1982-1991 (Box 8)
  - Kenney, Joan and John, 1981-1990 (Box 9)
  - Kirman, Alan, 1977-2010 (Box 9)
  - Kirman, Alan, 2004 (Box 72)
  - Kitching, Professor Beverly, 1979-1992 (Box 9)
  - Klassiker, 1997-2002 (Box 72)
  - Klein, Lawrence, 1980-2010 (Box 9)
  - Kneese and Krutilla, 1984-1990 (Box 9)
  - Koenig, Evan, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Kofi, Tetteh A., 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Kohlberg, Elon, 1973-1981 (Box 9)
  - Koopmans, T. C., 1982-1986 (Box 9)
  - Kornai, János, 1976-2008 (Box 9)
  - Kotlikoff, Larry, 2009 (Box 9)
  - Kottle, Darren, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
  - Kreicher, Larry, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - Krenzin, Kenneth Thomas, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Kreps, David, 1979-1997 (Box 9)
  - Kristol, W., 2009 (Box 9)
  - Kuan, Pin Lin, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Kuhn, Harold W., 1980-1988 (Box 9)
    Includes correspondence on Kuhn's edited volume on game theory
  - Kumar, Praveen, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Kunreuther, Howard, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Kuran, Timur, 1981-2010 (Box 9)
  - Kurz Dinner, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Kurz, Heinz, 1999-2002 (Box 9)
    Includes correspondence on classical growth model
  - Kurz, Mordecai, 1974-1994; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Kurz, Mordecai, 2000 (Box 72)
  - L, Misc. Correspondence, 1968-2010; 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Laffont, Jean-Jacques, 1979-2004 (Box 9)
  - Lai, Edwin, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Lancet, 2013 (Box 72)
  - Landau, Ralph, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Landes, David, 1982-1997 (Box 9)
  - Lane, John, 1968-1972 (Box 9)
  - Lang, Serge, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
  - Laroque, Guy, 1984-1989 (Box 9)
  - Lave, Charles, 1967-1972 (Box 9)
  - Lay, Joseph, 1981-1984 (Box 9)
  - Lederberg, Joshua, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Ledyard, John, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Leibenstein, Harvey, 1980 (Box 9)
  - Leonard, Robert J., 1991-2000 (Box 9)
  - Leontief, Wassily, 1975 (Box 9)
    Includes a note on the state of mathematical economics and the Econometric Society
  - Lesourne, Jacques, 1981-1991 (Box 9)
  - Leverich, Brian E., 1977 (Box 9)
  - Levhari, David, undated (Box 9)
  - Levin, Harvey J., 1985-1990 (Box 9)
  - Levin, Simon, 2009-2012 (Box 9)
  - Levinthal, Daniel, 1982-1988 (Box 9)
  - Levitt, Paul, 1974-1989; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Levy-Garboua, Vivien, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Lewis, Alain A., 1973-2002; 4 folders (Box 9)
    Includes correspondence on computability of general equilibrium and game theory
  - Lewis, Alain A., 1977-1996; 15 folders (Box 10)
    Includes correspondence on computability of general equilibrium, finite non-cooperative games, among other topics, and other routine correspondence
  - Lewis, Albert, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
  - Li Calzi, Marco, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
  - Li, Junjie Edward, 1991-2002 (Box 10)
  - Lieberman, Jerry, 1986-1993 (Box 10)
  - Light, Donald W., 1989 (Box 10)
  - Limes, Jack L., 1980-1991 (Box 10)
  - Lin, Kuan-Pin, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
  - Lindbeck, Assar, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Lines, Jack, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Lipset, S. M., 1998-2004 (Box 10)
  - Lombardo, Davide, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Lough, Erin, undated (Box 10)
  - Lucas, Robert E., 1980-1996 (Box 10)
  - Lumsden, Keith G., 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Lumsden, Keith G., The Esmee Fairbairn Research Center - Hariot-Watt University, 1979-1986 (Box 10)
  - Luo, Yuanzheng, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Lux Mundi, 1976 (Box 72)
  - M, Misc. Correspondence, 1976-1997; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - M.D - Ph.D, 2013 (Box 11)
  - Ma, 1990-2008 (Box 11)
  - Machina, Mark, 1982-2002 (Box 11)
  - Maier Inflation Project, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Malcomson, James, undated (Box 11)
  - Malinvaud, Edmond, 1977-2015 (Box 11)
  - Mandel, Michael, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Mandelbrot, Benoit, 1982-2004 (Box 11)
  - Mandler, Michael, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Mankin, Wyatt B., 1971-1991 (Box 11)
  - Manne, Alan S., 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Marchi, E., 1978-1992; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Margalit, Avishai, 2009 (Box 11)
  - Marglin, Stephen, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Margolis, Julius, 1970-1986; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Markham Publishing, 1963-1970 (Box 18)
  - Marks, David, undated (Box 11)
  - Marks, Robert E., 1988-1993 (Box 11)
  - Marschak, Jacob and Robert, 1980-1991 (Box 11)
  - Marschak Memoirs, 1983-1991 (Box 11)
    Includes correspondence on biography of Jacob Marschak
  - Marshall, John, 1979-1985 (Box 11)
  - Masch, Vladimir, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
  - Mas-Colell, Andreu, 1980-2014; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Maskin, Eric, 1975-2007; 2 folders (Box 11)
    Includes correspondence on social choice, mechanism design, and other routine correspondence
  - Masse, Pierre, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Mathematics in Education, 1990-1991 (Box 72)
  - Mathematics of Operations Research, 2003 (Box 72)
  - Mc, 1980-2006 (Box 11)
  - McAllister, Patrick, 1987-1989 (Box 11)
  - McCloskey, Deirdre, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
    Includes correspondence on McCloskey's work on critical evaluation of the field of economics
  - McCloskey, Donald, 1989-1991 (Box 11)
  - McKay, Chris, 1979 (Box 11)
  - McKenzie, Lionel, 1979-2002 (Box 11)
    Includes correspondence on McKenzie's presidential address to the Econometric Society and other routine correspondence
  - McLean, Iain, 1981-1993 (Box 11)
  - McNeil, Barbara, 1978-1992; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Me, 1978-2010 (Box 11)
  - Medina, Luis, 1978-1992; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Menell, Peter, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Mermerci, Mehmet A., 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1982-2002 (Box 11)
  - Messner, Steve, 2010 (Box 11)
  - Mesthene, Emmanuel G., undated (Box 11)
  - Metroeconomica, 1995 (Box 72)
  - Mezhlumian, A., 1997 (Box 11)
  - Milgrom, Paul Robert, 1980-1991 (Box 11)
  - Miller, Margaret, 1985-1988 (Box 11)
  - Miller, Ross, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Minhas, Bagicha, 1975-1994 (Box 11)
  - Mirowski, Philip, 1996-2000 (Box 11)
    Includes correspondence on Mirowski's work in the history of economics
  - MIT Press, 1985-1999 (Box 72)
  - Miyao, Takahiro, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Mo, Chi-Ping, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Mo, Jie-ping, 1986-2001; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Mo, Jie-ping, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Modigliani, Franco, 1984-1993 (Box 12)
  - Mohanan, Manoj, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Monroe, Kristen, undated (Box 12)
  - Montgomery, David, 1970-1982 (Box 12)
  - Monthly Review, 1981 (Box 72)
  - Morgan, Christol, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Morgenstern, Oskar, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Morishima, Michio, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Moss, Jonathan, 1987-1991 (Box 12)
  - Moss, Scott, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Moulin, Herve, 1984-1992 (Box 12)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1981-1992 (Box 12)
  - Mumford, Kevin, 2007-2013 (Box 12)
  - Myerson, Roger, 1974-1986; 3 folders (Box 12)
    Includes correspondence on bargaining and games and other routine correspondence
  - Myhrvold-Hanssen, T., 2000 (Box 12)
  - N, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2012; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Nakata, Hiroyuki, 2002-2004 (Box 12)
  - Nakatani, Iwao, 1973; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Namias, Jerome, 1981-1989 (Box 12)
  - Nasar, Sylvia, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Neff, Thomas L., 1985 (Box 12)
  - Negishi, Takashi, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Nehmer, Stanley, undated (Box 12)
  - Nerlove, Marc, 1966-1993; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Neuberg, Leland, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Nevo, Eviatar, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Newhouse, Joseph, 1973 (Box 72)
  - Newlon, Dan, 2009 (Box 12)
  - Neyman, Abraham, 1981-1991 (Box 12)
  - Nielsen, Carsten K., 1995-1999 (Box 12)
  - Nieri, Makato, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Nishino, Hisakazu, 1971-1973 (Box 12)
  - Nobel Channel, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Nobel Nominations, 2009-2012 (Box 72)
  - Noll, Roger, 1984-2001 (Box 12)
  - Nordhaus, William, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Norgaard, Richard B., 1995-2007 (Box 12)
  - North, Douglass C., 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - North-Holland Publishing Company, 1974-1988; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Novshek, William, 1985-1993 (Box 12)
  - Nozick, Robert, 1974 (Box 72)
    Includes correspondence about reviewing a book by Nozick.
  - O, Misc. Correspondence, 1975-2009; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - O'Hara, Ryan, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Ohashi, Isao, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Oi, Walter, 1983-1985 (Box 12)
  - Oiko Nomia, 1997-2011 (Box 72)
  - Ojala, J., 2009-2010 (Box 12)
  - Okafor, Chika, 2006-2011 (Box 12)
  - Okun, Arthur, 1979 (Box 12)
    Includes a brief note on rational expectations
  - Oleson, Kirsten, 2009-2011 (Box 12)
  - Omicron Delta Epsilon, 2006 (Box 12)
  - O'Reilly, Terrance, 1984-1990; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - O'Reilly, Terrance, 1988-1992 (Box 13)
  - Osana, Hiroaki, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
  - Ostrom, Elinor, 2001-2011 (Box 13)
  - Ostroy, Joseph, 1981-1989 (Box 13)
  - Owen, Robert, 2004-2006 (Box 13)
  - Oxford University Press, 1990-1993 (Box 18)
  - Oxford University Press, 1995-2007 (Box 72)
  - P, Misc. Correspondence, 1975-2009; 5 folders (Box 13)
  - Pacific Economic Journal, 1998-1999 (Box 72)
  - Panosian, C., 2009 (Box 13)
  - Panthaki, Farrakh, 1983-1991 (Box 13)
  - Papadoulos, Nicholas, 1978-1990; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Papandreou, Dr. George A., 1967-2006; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Parikh, Prashant, 1986-2012; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Parrillo, Richard Case, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Partisan Review, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Patel, N., 1995 (Box 13)
  - Patel, S., 2016 (Box 13)
  - Patinkin, Don, 1954-1995 (Box 13)
    Includes correspondence on Keynes's General Theory and other routine correspondence
  - Pattanaik, Prasanta K., 1988-1992 (Box 13)
  - Peace Economics, 2009 (Box 72)
  - Pedersen, Lasse, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Peleg, Bezalel, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Permissions, 2000-2015; 2 folders (Box 72)
    Reprint permissions granted
  - Pesotchinsky, Leon, 1980-1983 (Box 13)
  - Peterson, Louis D., 1971 (Box 13)
  - Phelps, Edmund S., 1980-2000 (Box 13)
  - Phelps, G. S., 2009 (Box 13)
  - Phillips, Tony, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Philosophia, 1976 (Box 72)
  - Philosophy and Public Affairs, 1981-1987 (Box 72)
  - Pitblado, Richard, 1985-1993 (Box 13)
  - Pliska, Stanley, 1980 (Box 13)
  - P'ng, Ivan, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Polemarchakis, Heraklis, 1975-2005; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Pope, Robin, 1985-2001; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Pope, Robin, 2012; 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Postlewaite, Andrew, 1980-1982 (Box 13)
  - Poterba, James, 1979-1984 (Box 13)
  - Prat, Andrea, 1996-2011 (Box 13)
  - Prazner, Elisha and David Schmeidler, 1972-1975 (Box 13)
  - Prescott, Edward, 1979 (Box 13)
    Includes copies of Prescott's work and other routine correspondence
  - Priebsch, Marcel, 2010 (Box 13)
  - Princeton University Press, 1989-1994 (Box 18)
  - Psomas, Andreas, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Pugh, David, 2010 (Box 13)
  - Q, Misc. Correspondence, 1981-2001; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Quantitative Finance, 2000-2004 (Box 73)
  - Questions from the Public, 1997 (Box 73)
  - Quint, Tom, 1991-1995; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - R, Misc. Correspondence, 1976-2015; 3 folders (Box 14)
  - R-T, Misc. Correspondence, 1984-2004 (Box 72)
  - Radner, Roy, 1974-2007; 3 folders (Box 14)
    Includes correspondence on information in economic decision-making and other routine correspondence
  - Raduchel Dissertation, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Raduchel, William J., 1977 (Box 14)
  - Ramey, Garey, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Rao, N. Koteswara, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Rapping, Leonard, 1980-1988 (Box 14)
  - Rassias, Themistocles M., 1990-1993 (Box 14)
  - Ratner, Sidney, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Raven, Peter H., 1984-1991 (Box 14)
  - Ray, Debraj, 1984-2002 (Box 14)
  - Raynaud, Herve - book, 1984-2010 (Box 14)
  - Recktenwald - Future, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Reder, Melvin, 1978 (Box 72)
  - Reich, Michael, 1971-1985; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Reprint Permissions, 1979-1999; 4 folders (Box 18)
    Reprint and translation permissions for previously published work
  - Resources for the Future, 1979-1984 (Box 18)
  - Restrepo, Professor R. A., 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - Review of Political Economy, 2003 (Box 73)
  - Richardson, Susan, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Rieder, Alyssa, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Riis, Christian, 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Riley, John, 1979-1988 (Box 14)
  - Rivera, Angel, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Riverside Case, 1983-1984 (Box 73)
    Correspondence on potential closure of heterodox department at UC - Riverside
  - Robertson III, James F., 1971 (Box 14)
  - Robinson Lectures, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Roemer, John E., 1980-1999 (Box 14)
  - Rogerson, Bill, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
  - Romer, Paul, 1993-2000 (Box 14)
  - Rosen, Sherwin, 1983-2001 (Box 14)
  - Rosenschein, Jeffrey S., 1985 (Box 14)
  - Ross, Lee, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Rossol, Joshua, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Roth, Alvin, 1980-1992 (Box 14)
  - Roughgarden, Jeffrey, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Routledge, 1989-1992 (Box 18)
  - Rowley, Jennifer L. - Thesis, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Rowman and Allenheld, 1985 (Box 72)
  - Rubinstein, Ariel, 1985-1989 (Box 14)
  - S, Misc. Correspondence, 1975-2008; 5 folders (Box 14)
  - S, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2009 (Box 15)
  - Saade, William, 1981-1988 (Box 15)
  - Salas, Fernando, 2012 (Box 15)
  - Sam, Savage, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Samuelson, Paul, 1974-2007 (Box 15)
    Includes brief correspondence on revealed preference and other routine correspondence
  - Samuelson, Paul, 1996 (Box 72)
    Includes a letter about an obituary of Karl Menger.
  - Santana, George, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Sarkis, Joseph-Eric Ziad, 1989-1998 (Box 15)
  - Satz, D., 2014 (Box 15)
  - Scarf, Herbert, 2007-2008 (Box 73)
  - Scarf, Herbert, 1977-2009 (Box 15)
  - Schaefer, Mark E., undated (Box 15)
  - Schelling, Thomas, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Schmidt, Stephen, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Schneider, Steve, 2010 (Box 15)
  - Schoenman, J. C., 1981 (Box 15)
  - Schoettle, Ferdinand P., 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Schreiner, Per, 1982-1992 (Box 15)
  - Schwarz, Michael, 1997-2006; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Selten, Richard, 1991-1995 (Box 15)
  - Sen, A., 1975-2009 (Box 15)
  - Sen, A., 2014 (Box 15)
  - Sent, Esther-Mirjam, 1993-2000 (Box 15)
  - Sen-Visva-Bharati, 1999 (Box 15)
  - Sethi, S., 2009-2010 (Box 15)
  - Shanmuga-Sundaram, Dr. Vedagiri, 1980-2013 (Box 15)
  - Shannon, Chris, 2009 (Box 15)
  - Shapiro, Joe, 2002-2008 (Box 15)
  - Shapley, Lloyd, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Shavell, Steven, 1976-2003 (Box 15)
  - Shell, Karl, 1977-2005 (Box 15)
  - Shell, Karl, 2001 (Box 73)
  - Shen, Ting, 1997-2006 (Box 15)
  - Shenkman, Yigal, 1996-1998 (Box 15)
  - Sherry, Edward, undated (Box 15)
  - Sheshinski, Eytian, 1976-2007; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Shiller, Robert, 2001-2009 (Box 15)
  - Shoham, Y., 1996-1998 (Box 15)
  - Shoven, John, 1994-2001 (Box 72)
  - Shubik, Martin, 1976-1985 (Box 15)
    Includes brief correspondence on economic exchange and other routine correspondence
  - Shum, K., 2014 (Box 15)
  - Simon, Herbert A., 1978-2001 (Box 15)
    Includes correspondence on limits of rationality, economic organization, and other routine correspondence
  - Sinclair, Stephen Mayer, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Skaf, Mazen, 1999 (Box 15)
  - Slutsky, Steven, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Smith, Anna D., 1997 (Box 15)
  - Smith, Vernon L., 1979-2002 (Box 15)
  - Social Choice and Welfare (Journal), 1982-2004 (Box 73)
  - Social Choice Chinese Translation, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Solow, Robert, 1990-2009 (Box 15)
    Includes correspondence on multi-sector growth models and other routine correspondence
  - Solow, Robert - Personal Correspondence, undated (Box 15)
  - Sonnenschein, Hugo, 1977-2000 (Box 15)
  - Spence, A. M., 1969-2001; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Squitieri, Ray, 1981-2002 (Box 15)
  - Stan, Peter, 1975-1978; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Staroselsky, V., 1975-1985 (Box 16)
  - Starr, Ross, 1966-2009; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Starrett, David A., 1977-1987; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Starrett, David A. - Personal, 1971-1976 (Box 16)
  - Stebbins, Eric, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Stefansson, Bjorn S., 1983-1987 (Box 16)
  - Steinberg, Danny, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Stiglitz, Joseph, 1994-2001 (Box 16)
  - Stigum, Bernt, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Stodolsky, David S., undated (Box 16)
  - Stoetzel, Jean, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
  - Stokey, Nancy, 1980-2004; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Stoleru, L., 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - Storelli, Claudio, 2004 (Box 16)
  - Strasnick, Steven, 1979-1982 (Box 16)
  - Such, Carol, 1981-2002 (Box 16)
  - Summer, R., 1995-1998 (Box 16)
  - Summers, Lawrence H., 1985-2006 (Box 16)
  - Sunder, A, 2014 (Box 16)
  - Sunstein, Cass, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Suppes, Patrick, 2014 (Box 16)
  - Suppes, Patrick - CV, 2004 (Box 16)
  - Suriyakumaran, Professor C., 1987 (Box 16)
  - Sutch, Richard, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Suzumura, Kotaro, 1984-2013 (Box 16)
  - Swedberg, Richard, 1986-1994 (Box 16)
    Includes correspondence on methodological individualism and economic sociology
  - Sweet, Victoria, undated (Box 16)
  - Swinton, David, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Sylos-Labini, Paolo, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Szenberg, Michael, 1994 (Box 16)
  - T, Misc. Correspondence, 1978-2011; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Takatoshi, Ito, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Taksar, Michael, 1982-2002 (Box 16)
  - Tamari, Meir, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Tandon, Pankaj, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Tauman, Yair, 1982-1996 (Box 16)
  - Taylor, John, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Taylor, John, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Telfor, S., 2008-2009 (Box 16)
  - Thain, Eric, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Thesis (Journal), 1994 (Box 73)
  - Thomson, William, 1981-1991 (Box 16)
  - Thornton, Charlotte, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Time Literary Supplement, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Tirole, Jean, 1982-2004 (Box 16)
  - Tisdell, Clement, 2015 (Box 16)
  - TLG Media, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Tobin, James, 1977-1987 (Box 16)
    Includes correspondence on Arrow declining to lead the Cowles Foundation and other routine correspondence
  - Tokimatsu, Koji, 2015 (Box 16)
  - Townsend, Robert M., 1980-1989 (Box 16)
  - Trosper, Ron, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Tsuru, Shigetu, 1981-2006 (Box 17)
  - Tullock, Gordon, 1974-1988 (Box 17)
    Includes correspondence on Arrow's Impossibility Theorem and Social Choice
  - Turnbull, Stephen J., 1984-1989 (Box 17)
  - Tversky, Amos, 1980-2003 (Box 17)
  - Tyrni, Ilari, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
  - Tyson, Christopher, 2001-2003 (Box 17)
  - Tyson, Laura, 1992-2002 (Box 17)
  - Tzevetanov, Ilia, 1985-1990 (Box 17)
  - U, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2005; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Uzawa, Hirofumi, 1980-2009; 2 folders (Box 17)
    Includes brief correspondence on stability of equilibrium in models with tradeable emissions and other routine correspondence
  - V, Misc. Correspondence, 1973-2010; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Varian, Hal, 2000 (Box 17)
  - Vazirani, Vijay, 2014 (Box 17)
  - Veinott, Arthur, 2009 (Box 17)
  - Vincent, Philip, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Vind, Karl, 1983-2003 (Box 17)
  - Virmani, Arvind, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Viscusi, W. Kip, 1978-2002; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - W, Misc. Correspondence, 1976-2009; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - W-Z, Misc. Correspondence, 1989-2000 (Box 72)
  - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1973-1989 (Box 18)
  - Wakabayashi, Nobuo, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Walker, David K., 1993 (Box 17)
  - Wallenstein, Gerd, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Walzer, Michael, 1993 (Box 17)
  - War Department, 1946 (Box 72)
    Includes a letter written by Arrow to the U.S. War Department on economics textbook choices.
  - War Resistors International, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Warsh, David, 1992-2006 (Box 17)
  - Weber, Thomas, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Webster, Michael, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Weibull, Jörgen, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Weiner, Jonathan, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Weinstein, Milton, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Weintraub, E. Roy, 1982-2007 (Box 17)
    Includes brief correspondence on the history of general equilibrium
  - Weintraub, E. Roy, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Weisbrod, Burton, 2009 (Box 17)
  - Weiss, Laurence, 1980-1984 (Box 17)
  - Weiss, Uri, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Weisskopf, Thomas, 1983-1987 (Box 17)
  - Weitzman, Martin, 1998 (Box 17)
    Includes correspondence on time discounting
  - Werbos, Paul, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Werfel, S., 2012 (Box 17)
  - Wesson Latin America, 1987 (Box 17)
  - White, Lawrence H., undated (Box 17)
  - Wignjowijoto, Hartojo, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Wilensky, Daniel, 2015 (Box 17)
  - Williams, Priscila, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Williamson, Jeffrey, 1979-1981 (Box 17)
  - Williamson, Olivier, 1982-2012 (Box 17)
    Includes correspondence on Coase and transaction costs as well as other routine correspondence
  - Wilson, Robert, 1993-2013 (Box 17)
  - Wolnowicz, R., undated (Box 17)
  - Wolpert, David, 2012 (Box 17)
  - Wood, Robert O., 1984-1992 (Box 17)
  - Wooders, Myrna, 1985-2007 (Box 18)
  - Wu, Ho-Mou, 1980-1997 (Box 18)
  - X, Misc. Correspondence, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Xiao, Mingjun, 2014 (Box 18)
  - Xiaoming, Pan, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Xing, Yiqing, 2010 (Box 18)
  - XYZ, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2012; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Y, Misc. Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 18)
  - Yaari, Menahem, 1980-1994 (Box 18)
  - Yang, X., 1999-2000 (Box 18)
  - Yanofsky, Neal, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Yellen, Janet, 1979-2013 (Box 18)
  - Yellin, Joel, 1981-1984 (Box 18)
  - Yotopoulos, Pan, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Young, Peyton H., 1979-2003 (Box 18)
  - Zafarullah, Mohammad, 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Zame, William, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Zeckhauser, Richard, 1979-1999 (Box 18)
  - Zweiman, Ari, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Zygmunt Gebethner Polish Scientific Publisher, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence electronic records, 1999-2016; 313 files; 13 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0002)
    Restricted until 2026. Contact Research Services to request access from Arrow's family.
- Email Correspondence, 1999-2017 and undated
  Contains email messages from Arrow's email inbox. Messages between 1999 and 2009 were exported from the Eudora email client, while messages 2009-2017 were exported from Apple Mail. Messages are organized annually, and further divided into files for Arrow's incoming and outgoing correspondence.
  Messages are accessible in their current format, but may benefit from additional treatment as email processing tools reach greater levels of stability.
  - Email Correspondence, 1999; 26 messages, less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence
  - Email Correspondence, 2000; 181 messages, less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence, notable correspondents include Roy Radner, Paul Samuelon, Armen Alchian
  - Email Correspondence, 2001; 1220 messages, 7 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence, notable correspondents include Kotaro Suzumura, Partha Dasgupta, James K. Galbraith
  - Email Correspondence, 2002; 1877 messages, 12 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence, notable correspondents include Partha Dasgupta, Roy Radner, James Heckman
  - Email Correspondence, 2003; 1678 messages, 9 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence, notable correspondents include Paul Ehrlich, Partha Dasgupta, Michael Intriligator, Steven Durlauf
  - Email Correspondence, 2004; 1988 messages, 14 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence, notable correspondents include Michael Intriligator, Steven Durlauf, Partha Dasgupta, Kotaro Suzumura
  - Email Correspondence, 2005; 3254 messages, 206 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)
    Includes professional and personal correspondence, notable correspondents include Peter Diamond, Paul Ehrlich, Simon Levin, Steven Durlauf
  - Email Correspondence, 2006; 3608 messages, 350 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0001)